John Lee

Frontend | Blockchain developer

Ontario Canada +1 354 800 4895 whistlingman411@gmail.com

Summary

I specialize in end-to-end development of software systems using the latest technologies to build Blockchain and web platforms of any kind. Also I'm a relentless problem-solver with an insatiable urge to learn, sociable, quick study, and a passionate novelist by hobby. With my 8 years of rich experience in Full stack and Blockchain development, my skill set includes:

- ✓ JavaScript, jQuery, TypeScript
- ✓ PHP, Laravel, Wordpress, Magento
- ✓ Shopify, Shopify plus
- ✓ Nodejs, Expressjs, Reactjs, Nextjs, Vuejs, Nuxtjs, Web3js
- ✓ MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, NoSQL
- ✓ Amazon Web Service, Docker, GraphQL, Vagrant
- ✓ Blockchain-Ethereum and Hyperledger
- ✓ SmartContract (ERC20, ERC21, ERC721, ERC721A, ERC1155)
- ✓ DApps development (Solidity/Rust)

As a Senior Full Stack and Blockchain developer, I will find an effective, timely solution to your problem - and that's a promise.

Work experience

PHP developer 2017/10 - 2018/04

Parmer Agency

I have developed 30+ websites using PHP frameworks such as Laravel, Codeigniter, Zend, Wordpress and Magento. At that time, I focused developing E-Commerce platforms using PHP language. I have made 100+ wordpress and magento custom extensions and built 15+ ecommerce sites from PSD design.

Senior Frontend developer

2018/06 - 2020/11

Velox Agency

I have built 25+ web projects using React, Vue, Next, Nuxt and Node. Also I have built 20+ E-Commerce stores using Shopify. I am proud of my Front end and Shopify skills my self.

Senior Full Stack developer

2021/03 - 2022/09

Vyudu Agency

Working as a full stack developer in this agency. I have made 30+ web projects using Javascript and php frameworks such as React, Vue, Node, Nest, Expressjs, Laravel and Codeigniter. I prefer to use Vue as frontend and Laravel and backend. Also I have used MongoDB and PostgreSQL for my MERN, MEAN, MEVN projects.

Blockchain developer

2022/11 - 2023/08

Vault3D

As a New Era's developer, I have made deep knowledge of Blockchain first and dive into this market place. Vault3D is my first project that I have built from Figma design and made contracts written by Solidity.

Education

The University of Hong Kong

Featured Projects

BigASSFans 2018/01 - 2018/04

Parmer Agency

Wordpress project that has been built by me from PSD design. I have used DIVI theme and 15+ plugins for this store. Also made 3 custom plugins for completing this project. This store is fully responsive with fast speed. I have built 30+ ecommerce sites with php but this is one of my best market place that has been built by me.

DCG onboarding 2018/07 - 2018/11

Velox Agency

As a senior Frontend developer, I have built this website using Node, React and firebase. This is one kind of subscribing system working with stripe. I have done this project successfully with tight deadline.

Muzzle-Loaders Shop

2019/08 - 2020/10

Velox Agency

As a senior shopify developer, I have convert muzzle-loaders.com store from Magento 2.3 to Shopify plus without any trouble. Import data from Magento store and build front pages with new figma design. MZ magento store contains 10k customers and 15k products data but it transferred to shopify without any trouble. It takes only 2 months for complete Shopify store.

FamilyTree365 2021/07 - 2022/05

Vyudu Agency

As a Lead developer, I have built this web project using php,Laravel (for backend) and Nuxtjs (for frontend). This project is for creating family tree easily with visual interface. My role was lead developer in this team.

Vault3D 2023/02 - 2023/07

Vault3D

As a Senior full stack and Blockchain developer, I have built this store using React, Node, Firebase and TailwindCSS. This store contains minting and staking functionalities written by solidity. It takes 2 months for completing this project.

Skills

Blockchain

As a new era's web developer, I have 3 years of experience with blockchain development. I have built several NFT market places using React and Vue. Nowadays, I focus working with web3js.

Database

With my 10+ years of computer programming experience, I am very familiar with several kind of database management systems such as Oracle, Mysql, Postgresql, Mongodb and Firebase.

Javascript

As a senior full stack developer, I have 6 years of rich experience in working with javascript frameworks such as React, Vue, Nuxt, Next, Express, Node. Also I am very familiar with using Typescript.

PHP

With my 8 years of rich experience in php development, I have built 50+ web projects using PHP frameworks such as Laravel, Codeigniter and Zend.

Created with 📅 VisualCV